Friends, there is a lot of competition in health insurance.
Where there is competition,
only the customer benefits.
Friends, companies are bringing new products
to the market so that they can do
more business and
give maximum benefits to the customer.
Friends, through this video I am going to do a complete comparison of the features and benefits of two
best
[music]
insurance
ICICI Lombard Health Advantage Plans.
And I promise you that if you watch this video,
you can do something for yourself and your family.
Friends, do
not skip this very important video. If you
skip it, you will miss an important point
and you will
not be able to take the best decision for your family.
If you are visiting for the first time, then
subscribe to the channel so that I upload such
interesting videos every week
on my channel. And after
watching those videos, you can take the best health and
financial decision for yourself and your
family today. Friends, if
you are on the best health insurance or
best health number  You can contact us.
You will get the best support from our team
and if you have any inquiry, you can
contact me directly through WhatsApp.
Friends, recently I uploaded a lot of
videos on my channel regarding
health insurance, regarding
termination and regarding
SAP mutual funds. Now
you can check out the videos. I
think by watching those videos you
can also take your best decision.
[Music] If
anyone does health insurance, when we go to
purchase a mediclaim policy,
then we see how many network
hospitals are there with the company. If we
talk about network hospitals, then the network
hospitals of the company which are on the panel with them are
8700 hospitals. If we talk about
ICICI Lombard, their panel
hospitals are on the cashless panel, then there are
501 hospitals on the panel. Friends,
if we talk about TPL, both have
in-house TPA. Right, now while talking, I
mean, what is the minimum policy that you
can purchase?  How much is included except, if we
talk about the above, the minimum is up to 5 lakhs
and the maximum that can go up to
Walt Road, you can take the minimum,
they have ₹5 lakhs and the
maximum that you can
take is up to 3 crores. Friends,
if we talk about entries, a
child who is 91 days old can be an
Android in the policy and the
maximum date is that if any person is up to 65 years old, then he
can enter in this plan. Further,
if we take ICICI Lombard's
Help Advantage plan, the minimum
entry is 91 days and the maximum that
any person up to 65 years old can enter.
[Music]
Friends, now let's talk about dependent child, that is,
any child that we add in the family photo
with the husband and wife, if
we add a child, then the minimum
entry is 91 days and the maximum that the
child can stay with the family folder.
That health insurance on Nibbon which is
in their RE plan,
if there is a child of 30 years then he can live together in the family plot,
after that his individual
policy is formed. If there is a child of 25 years in the
health advantage plan of ICC Lombard, then the maximum number of children
who can live
together is that if there is a child of 25 years then he can
live together.
Friends, if we talk about the term,
how many years term can it be, now you can take a
term of 2 years or 3 years, which is
on Nibbon, you can take this plan in such a plan, like there is
no discount in one year, additional
discount is available, if you take a 2 year policy then additional
discount
is available in 3 years and a little more
discount is available. In fact, if you take a
term of 1 year, 2 year or 3 years in ICICI Lombard's Health Advantage, you
can take off.
Friends, now let's talk about the room rate category.
In any medical, the
maximum charges that are levied in health insurance,
this room rent is approximately Rs.  You can say that the
charges of room rent are levied from 25% to 40% to 50%. If any
claim comes, then you can check it. So
if we talk about the room rent category, that is,
lemon, there is no limit on room rent in all these plans.
If
you look at the ICICI Health Advantage Plan
also, there is no capping or limit on room rent.
You can take a room of other categories.
So this is the biggest plus point in
both plans. Right
friends, now let's talk about the
surgeries that are basically
supported. There are some modern
treatments today, like stone hernia, catheterectomy,
what happens in them. Basically, you are admitted
but there is no need for 24 hours of breathing.
If you go for 2 hours, 3 hours,
4 hours, then if you get discharged in 8 hours, 10 hours, then the
treatment is also covered. So,
in both, the old treatment is covered. Right,
if the treatment is closed, the company's treatment covers all the treatment.
Friends, now let's talk about refill benefit.
Refill means that suppose you
have 10
lakhs, Mr. Man, take 10 lakhs and you have paid that amount.
Now if some other person falls sick, then let's
claim them. Suppose a claim of 10 lakhs is made, then from
where will you get it? If it is 2 lakhs to
25 lakhs, then the company refills it from
time to time. It should be refilled from time to time. So the
biggest plus point is that in Nibhahu's
health insurance, whatever diesel is consumed by the person gets
refilled
and there is no limit in it. It can be refilled
unlimited number of times. This is the real
statement in this policy. And
if you
talk about ICICI Lombard's health advantage, then theirs will be full, but once it is
vanished, then only
10 lakhs will be refilled. So if a
comparison is seen in this, then the unlimited refill
option is available in the above mentioned areas.
Suppose someone  Any fiber boy, right, so fever
and what normally happens, paracetamol
procedure etc. is taken after that the
fever does not subside, then what happened, that the doctor went to the doctor, the
doctor prescribed some tests,
after that it was found that there is some other problem,
right, so what is the problem, that the fever is
not subsiding, then you will have to get admitted in the hospital, so
before that when we get
admitted in the hospital, that will definitely be covered in cashless,
but before that whatever
treatment we got, we paid from our pocket, so whatever
we paid is the expenses of 60 days before
and after discharge, whatever other
long-term medicines are there for 6 months, that
means
whatever medicine or concentration will be there, that will
also be covered by the company, right, in the Racer plan,
168, its prone post horseplasia
is covered and if there is
health advantage of this ICICI Lombard, in that also there
is coverage up to 60 and 180 days,
friends, now let's talk about domiciliary
hospital,
hospital means this, suppose I will give an
example  If I go to a village, then the
patient cannot be seen,
so now what happens is that
if the treatment is done under the supervision of a registered MBBS, then
that treatment is called domicile retirement,
so in both the companies, the domicile treatment which
is covered, up to the deductible, right
friends, if you talk about NCB i.e.
knocking bonus, then in the plan, the bonus
from the job is 50%, if you have taken a policy of 10 lakhs, I am
telling you an example, then the next
year the bonus will increase, this 5 lakhs means the
baseline bonus will be added, then next year another
50% will be added, that is, 5 lakhs will be added, that is,
in 2 years your
police job bonus of 10 lakhs will be added,
if we talk about the health insurance of ICICI Lombard, the
bonus for law in ICICI Lombard will increase by 20%,
and if it is for the body, then 10 lakhs will be added, that
day for 5 years, friends, now let's talk about
emergency road ambulance, ₹2000 which is
in nibopa health insurance and 1% off
Sami-shirt maximum up to 10000 roadside
ambulance assistant will be available
air polish will be available maximum of 2.5 lakh reverse
point will be and
in ICICI Lombard up to D time-sodi right
friends now let's talk about
help checkup of 500
and the maximum will be ₹10000
if we look at virus
in ICICI Lombard it is 0.5% in them also the
maximum will be ₹10000 right friends now let's
talk about current owner, you have cupboard in both so let's
talk about iOS treatment both
planning I/O statement is covered up you
leave it in sir now friends let's talk about
worldwide coverage then there is
no worldwide coverage in ICICI Lombard virus if we talk about
worldwide health
insurance coverage in ICICI Lombard but for that
you will have to take 25 lakh and above
facility of worldwide coverage is available for deposit
right now friends let's talk about which
mobile like there are many
hospitals on consumer, very many  Charges like
gloves etc. are not in the cupboard.
This consumable item is called non-medical expenses.
So, the
option of Safeguard rider is available. If you take this rider, then
your consumerical items will
also be covered, like non-medical expenses,
all those things will be covered.
If you opt for the Claim Product Rider in ICICI Lombard also, then
your
non-medical expenses will also be covered there.
You can take it, in which you can cover OPD as well.
If you
want to cover this in ICICI Lombard also, then it
is covered there as well. Now you can cover the
additional benefits which you
can avail from it. You can take
hospital cash, maximum both the
partial benefits are in the zones.
Delhi and NCR Mumbai, these types of
cities come under Zone 1 and Zone 2 includes the rest
of India and other
cities, from the smaller cities to the smaller ones, in which the
police stations are famous for themselves there.  It is
cheaper if you want to get treatment in daily
or in zone wise, there is
no copayment required there.
If you see, there is 22% copper mint.
If
you take a policy in ICICI Lombard, then if you
take a policy in lower zone, for example, if
you take a policy in the smallest series, if you
want to travel to metro cities, then it will have a right
wear. If we talk about riders, then
you can take riders in ICICI Lombard, in
which you can take maternity rider,
additional rider which you can take in health add.
Friends,
if we take any medical plan, then there is a waiting
period in it, so it is very important for you to know about the waiting period. So,
in both the plans, the
initial waiting period is
basically 30 days. If there is
any normal disease, then the
cover will start after 30 days. So, in both the plans, there is an
initial waiting period of 38 days. For specific
illnesses like suppositories, cataract, hernia, stone,
these planning surgeries, then after 2 years  It is
covered, basically both also have a
waiting period of 24 months, right now if we talk about pre-
existing disease, then if there is any
pre-existing disease, if we
talk about ICICI Lombard in 36, then
whatever is there after 24 marks is covered, so
friends, this was
health insurance and
comparison on lemon, out of this you tell me which
plan is best for you, which plan
you liked, if any topic is left in between, then
you can WhatsApp me,
I will definitely answer you, I will answer you,
friends if you like the video then
share it with your friends and so that they can
also get good knowledge, so that they can
take the best decision for their health,
if you have not subscribed to the channel yet, then do it
because
you will get such interesting videos on my channel
and you will be able to take the best decision,
friends if you want to take the best health insurance for
students or any mutual
funds, then you
can contact us through WhatsApp, you will
get the best services from us, if there is
anything else then we will discuss it in the next video
If you
want me to make videos on some other topic, you
can comment so that I can
make videos on other topics. Thank you so much, thanks
for watching this video. See you
in the next video with a great topic.
And thank you so much, thanks for
watching this video. Jai Hind Vande Mataram
[Music]